const questions = [
  {
    question: "What is the capital of France?",
    options: ["Paris", "London", "Berlin", "Madrid"],
    correctAnswer: 0, //"Paris",
  },
  {
    question: "_____ was formely referred to as NyasaLand.",
    options: ["Congo", "Seychelles", "Madagascar", "Malawi"],
    correctAnswer: 3, //"Malawi",
  },
  {
    question: "Nigeria gain her independence on October 1st ____?",
    options: ["1914", "1960", "1956", "1963"],
    correctAnswer: 1, //"1960",
  },
  {
    question: "____ and ____ are countries in West Africa",
    options: [
      "Zimbabwe and Ghana",
      "Sudan and Uganda",
      "Sudan and South-Sudan",
      "Chad and Guinea-Bissau",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3, //"Chad and Guinea-Bissau",
  },
  {
    question: "All these countries are North Africa countries except _____",
    options: ["Algeria", "Mali", "Egpyt", "Morrocco"],
    correctAnswer: 1, //"Mali",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the capital of France?",
    options: ["Paris", "London", "Berlin", "Madrid"],
    correctAnswer: 0, //"Paris",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the capital of Sierra-Leone?",
    options: ["Timbuktu", "London", "Freetown", "Lagos"],
    correctAnswer: 2, //"Freetown",
  },
  {
    question: "What does Porphyrophile stands for?",
    options: [
      "Confidence",
      "Love for color purple",
      "Fear of color purple",
      "Love for colors",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1, //"Love for color purple",
  },
  {},
  {
    question: "What year is the Berlin conference?",
    options: ["1885", "1884", "1997", "1202"],
    correctAnswer: 0, //"1885",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The partioning of Africa and sharing it resources among European powers was done at ...",
    options: [
      "UN Conference",
      "International Conference",
      "Berlin Conference",
      "WWII",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2, //"Berlin Conference",
  },
  {
    question: "The United Nations(UN) is preceded by which body?",
    options: [
      "OAU(Organization of African Unity)",
      "WHO(World Health Organization)",
      "European Union (EU)",
      "League of Nations",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3, //"League of Nations",
  },
  {
    question: "The commonwealth countries are colonized by?",
    options: ["Britain", "Germany", "Russia", "France"],
    correctAnswer: 0, //"Britain",
  },
];

export default questions;
